question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The surface area of Russia is slightly larger than that of the dwarf planet Pluto.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The Japanese Shinkansen beat the French TGV&#039;s speed record for fastest electric rail train.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The colour of the pills in the Matrix were Blue and Yellow.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Japanese god Izanagi successfully returned his wife Izanami from the Underworld.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
